(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T21:47:21.448600",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question of "Do you love me?",
笑顔で返すしかできない。
I can only reply with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように、私の答案を君は待っている。
As if teased by a demon, you are waiting for my answer.
放課後の教室に、君だけを残す時間が好き。
I love the time when I leave only you in the classroom after school.
ふたりきりになっても許される理由になるでしょ、ねぇ。
It's a valid reason to be alone together, right?
きっと女生徒のように隣を歩けないのは、
Surely, the reason I can't walk beside you like a female student
待つ制服に、揺れる白衣。それがふたりの距離だから。
is the waiting uniform and swaying lab coat. That's the distance between us.
熱くなるほど幼い心がばれちゃわないように、
So that my burning, childish heart isn't exposed,
君にとっての先生になるフリして担う、秘密のクラス。
I pretend to be a teacher to you in our secret class.
「好きですか」の難題に、笑顔で返すしかできない。
To the difficult question of "Do you love me?", I can only reply with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように、私の答案を君は待っている。
As if teased by a demon, you are waiting for my answer.
や らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱ
Ya rari-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa
らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱららぱ
lali-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa-la-pa
純粋が仇になる世界で
In a world where purity becomes a curse,
や らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱ
ya rari-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa
らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱららぱ
lali-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa-la-pa
また来週も戦えるかな
I wonder if I can fight again next week?
可愛い衣装纏って 決めポーズで光って
Wearing a cute outfit, shining in a decided pose,
ピュアな想い魔法に変えて
Turning pure feelings into magic,
みんなの平和願って 邪悪に立ち向かって
Wishing for everyone's peace, standing up against evil—
それを匿名はディスった
Anonymous people dissed that.
「本当は〇〇なんですか？」
"Aren't you actually a XX?"
「ぶっちゃけ〇〇なんですか？」
"To be honest, are you a XX?"
自分自身がそう思うから
Because you think that way yourself,
みんな〇〇であって欲しいんです
You want everyone to be XX too.
そんな手垢のついた よくある風評で
With such worn-out, common rumors,
錆びつく魔法のステッキ
My magic wand is rusting away.
知らん知らん
I don't know, I don't know!
はぁ 正直もう止めたい （はぁ）
Ah, honestly I want to quit already (Ah)
魔法少女をやめたい （はぁ）
I want to quit being a magical girl (Ah)
誰が敵か味方かわからないし
I don't know who is friend or foe,
「陰険」で「強欲」で「滑稽」で「外道」で
"Devious," "greedy," "ridiculous," "outrageous"—
魔法がとけるチョコみたいに
Like chocolate melting away, my magic dissolves.
や らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱ
Ya rari-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa
らりぱっぱらぱっぱららぱららぱ
Lali-pap-pala-pa-pala-la-pa-la-pa
純粋が仇になる世界で
In a world where purity becomes a curse,
はぁ 正直もう止めたい （はぁ）
Ah, honestly I want to quit already (Ah)
魔法少女をやめたい （はぁ）
I want to quit being a magical girl (Ah)
もう好きな人だけ守っていたい
I just want to protect the people I love.
や だんだんディだん だんだんディだん
Ya dan-dan-di-dan, dan-dan-di-dan
これでいい。
This is fine.
君のために
For your sake.
そう決めたのに
Even though I decided that,
去る制服へ、煌く白衣。
To the leaving uniform, the shining white coat.
思わず君を引き止める。
I unconsciously hold you back.
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question "Do you love me?",
許されない答案を書いた。
I wrote an unacceptable answer.
君の将来を縛るだけの
A single promise of love that's nothing more
独り善がりな、恋の約束。
Than selfishly binding your future.
ただ君の悲しむ顔を
If I didn't have to see your sad face anymore,
もう見送らなくていいなら、
If I didn't have to watch you leave,
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい。
Even if I'm called a demon, it's fine.
甘く溶けるようなひとときをあなたに。
Giving you a sweetly melting moment.
これでいい。
This is fine.
君のために
For your sake.
そう決めたのに
Even though I decided that,
去る制服へ、煌く白衣。
To the leaving uniform, the shining white coat.
思わず君を引き止める。
I unconsciously hold you back.
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question "Do you love me?",
許されない答案を書いた。
I wrote an unacceptable answer.
君の将来を縛るだけの
A single promise of love that's nothing more
独り善がりな、恋の約束。
Than selfishly binding your future.
ただ君の悲しむ顔を
If I didn't have to see your sad face anymore,
もう見送らなくていいなら、
If I didn't have to watch you leave,
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい。
Even if I'm called a demon, it's fine.
甘く溶けるようなひとときをあなたに。
Giving you a sweetly melting moment.
聞いてみたいの 飛んでって
I want to hear it, fly away,
少しも不器用くらいに 骨折たり
Even if it's a bit clumsy...
寝た時聴いてみて 受け取って
Listen to it when you sleep, receive it,
甘くとろけちゃうような 時も
Even at times when it melts so sweetly.
疲れてる顔をして いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
Showing a tired face, you always work so hard,
もう全て任せて 全部食べてあげようか
Leave everything to me, shall I eat it all up for you?
余裕なんていらないよ ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
You don't need composure, you've got to look straight at me.
目と目が合うでしょ 照れちゃうくらいに見つめてね
Our eyes will meet, right? Look at me until you get shy.
一つ 無邪気にさせて
Let me make you innocent one by one,
二つ 見つけてね
Find them two by two,
取りこにしちゃうの 心拍数急上昇
Captivating you, your heart rate skyrocketing!
好きよ
I love you!
聞いてみたいの 飛んでって
I want to hear it, fly away,
不安な顔より笑顔を見せて
Show me a smile instead of an anxious face,
ねえちゃんと聴いてみて 受け取って
Hey, listen carefully, receive it,
甘いチョコのような時も ここにいたいのに
Even at times like sweet chocolate, even though I want to stay here,
もう困っちゃう ぶっちゃけにしちょっぴり
I'm already troubled, quite frankly a little bit
胸きゅん散らしちゃうわ よしよしでももっと
Scattering heartthrobs, pat pat, but even more
君の声をもっと聞かせて
Let me hear your voice even more,
不安なんて抱えてらしくないなんて思ってた
Thinking it's unlike you to hold such anxiety,
全部全部丸ごと包み込んでとかしてあげる
I'll wrap you up completely and melt you down.
聞いてみたいの 飛んでって
I want to hear it, fly away,
不安な顔より笑顔を見せて
Show me a smile instead of an anxious face,
ねえちゃんと聴いてみて 受け取って
Hey, listen carefully, receive it,
甘いチョコのような時も ここにいたいのに
Even at times like sweet chocolate, even though I want to stay here,
もう困っちゃう ぶっちゃけにしちょっぴり
I'm already troubled, quite frankly a little bit
胸きゅん散らしちゃうわ よしよしでももっと
Scattering heartthrobs, pat pat, but even more
君の声をもっと聞かせて
Let me hear your voice even more,
不安なんて抱えてらしくないなんて思ってた
Thinking it's unlike you to hold such anxiety,
全部全部丸ごと包み込んでとかしてあげる
I'll wrap you up completely and melt you down.
どうだって 何したって
No matter what I do, no matter what happens,
気持ちは同じなんだね
our feelings are the same, right?
ここだって どこだって
Right here, or anywhere,
想いは伝わるから
my feelings will reach you,
声にして 文字にして
put into words, put into writing,
勇気出して 好きって伝えてよ
gather your courage and tell me you love me.
今日だって いつだって ああ
Today, always, ah,
愛し返すの
I'll love you back.
隠さないで ちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me properly,
君のこと全部を
everything about you,
ちょうだい
give it to me.
聴いて 会いたいすぐ飛んできて
Listen, I want to see you, fly right over,
少しこまるくらいにお願い
enough to trouble me a little bit,
叶えるココロ 聞いてみて 感じてほしいの
listen to my heart granting your wish, feel it.
会いたいすぐ飛んできて
I want to see you, fly right over,
少しこまるくらいにおねだりねだっちゃって
begging enough to trouble me a little bit,
受け取って あまっとろけちゃうようなときを 隣にいたいから
accept it, I want to be by your side during those sweetly melting moments.
みんなー！今日は来てくれてありがとー！
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming today!
どうも、和月ちょこ活動4周年記念ライブっていただいて、みんな盛り上がってるー？
Thank you for having my Yuzuki Choco 4th Anniversary LIVE! Is everyone getting hyped?
いやオープニングね、ちょこ、ちょこのね、オリジナル曲2曲目歌っちゃったんだけど、どうだった？やっぱちょこのオリジナル曲みんな好きだよね？ちょこ私好き。
For the opening, I sang my second original song! How was it? You all love my original songs, right? I love them too.
はい、ということでね、今回は歌ライブ、ちょっとね前回味締めて、2回目やろうかなと思って、ちょっと隠してみたんだけど、この後はね、みんなを呼んでみんなといろいろとね歌うのでぜひぜひみなさまこのまま盛り上がって行くぞー！
So this time, it's a singing live! After getting a taste last time, I thought about doing a second one and kept it secret. But after this, I'm calling everyone up to sing together, so let's keep getting hyped!
それでは、みんなのこと呼んで来るから、ちょっと待っててね！
So, I'm going to go call everyone, please wait a moment!
今日から君の好きなとこ一日一個伝えよ
Starting today, I'll tell you one thing I love about you every single day,
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ バッキューン
making your heart race 365 times! Bang!
小悪魔だってかまわない！ 作詞・作曲：HoneyWorks
[Title: It's Okay to Be a Little Devil! / Music & Lyrics: HoneyWorks]
こっちに置いてよもう もしかしてまだ片思い？
Put your attention here! Could it be that it's still unrequited?
たまに甘えてくるくせに もしかしててころがされてる？
Even though you act spoiled sometimes, are you just playing me?
ひと目惚れして 毎日通ってだ
Falling in love at first sight, visiting every single day,
君と目が合うたびに恋が爆発
every time our eyes meet, love explodes.
今日から君の好きなとこ一日一個伝えよ
Starting today, I'll tell you one thing I love about you every single day,
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ バッキューン
making your heart race 365 times! Bang!
他の子を見たり 別の男を見たり
Looking at other girls, or looking at other guys,
君だけ見てるよ えらいのこほびはチュー
I'm only looking at you! A good boy reward is a kiss.
たまにはお出かけと いつも部屋デートばかりじゃん
Sometimes let's go out, instead of always indoor dates!
もちろんそれでもいいけど 僕だってオシャレしたいし
Of course that's fine too, but I want to dress up nicely as well.
嫉妬やだ…
Jealousy is annoying...
今日から君の好きなとこ 一日一個伝えよう
Starting today, let's share one thing
I love about you every single day!
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ(バキュン！)
I'll make your heart race 365 times a year! (Bang!)
「こっちにおいでよ」もう…
"Stay right here with me,"
もしかしてまだ片思い？
Could it be that you still have a crush on me?
たまに甘えてくるくせに
Even though you sometimes let me pamper you,
もしかして転がされてる？
Could it be that you're playing hard to get?
一目惚れして 毎日通ってた
I fell for you at first sight,
君と目が合う度に 恋が爆発
And my love explodes every time our eyes meet!
今日から君の好きなとこ 一日一個伝えよう
Starting today, let's share one thing
I love about you every single day!
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ(バキュン！)
I'll make your heart race 365 times a year! (Bang!)
他の子を見たり？(ノンノン)
Checking out other girls? (No, no!)
携帯ばっかり見たり？(ノンノン)
Always glued to your phone? (No, no!)
君だけ見てるよ
I only have eyes for you!
偉いご褒美は？(チュウ)
Where's my praise and reward? (Chu!)
「たまにはお出かけどう？」
"How about going out somewhere?"
いつも部屋デートばかりじゃん？
We always just stay in for room dates, don't we?
もちろんそれでもいいけど
Sure, that's fine too,
僕だってオシャレスタイルしだし
But I want to dress up nicely sometimes as well!
気分屋な君
With your fickle mood,
ああ世話が焼けるな
Oh, it's such a handful to deal with.
僕がいないと何もできないくせに
Even though you'd be helpless without me,
毎日君の機嫌取って
I cater to your every mood every day,
一日いっぱいハグして
Hugging you all day long,
何百回何千回愛を伝えちゃうぜ(バキュン！)
And telling you I love you hundreds, thousands of times! (Bang!)
独りにしちゃったり(ノンノン)
Keeping it all to myself? (No, no!)
ゲームばっかりしたり(ノンノン)
Playing games all the time? (No, no!)
君だけ見てるよ
I only have eyes for you!
偉いご褒美は？(チュウ)
Where's my praise and reward? (Chu!)
帰り遅くなりそうだけど
I know it's going to be late on the way back,
急いで帰るからね
But I'm rushing straight home,
寄り道せずに愛の巣
Heading straight back to our nest of love without stopping!
「ただいまー！」
"I'm home!"
“おかえり”もナシ？
No "welcome back"?
“よしよし”もナシ？
No "there, there"?
それでもいいよ だから一緒にいてね
Even so, it's fine, so let's stay together!
ねえねえ どこ隠れてるの？
Hey, hey, where are you hiding?
もしかして出てきちゃっていい？
Could it be that you came out to meet me?
急に飛びついてきた
You rushed right out to greet me,
君は小悪魔だね
You're such a little devil!
今日から君の好きなとこ 一日一個伝えよう
Starting today, let's share one thing
I love about you every single day!
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ(バキュン！)
I'll make your heart race 365 times a year! (Bang!)
他の子を見たり？(ノンノン)
Checking out other girls? (No, no!)
携帯ばっかり見たり？(ノンノン)
Always glued to your phone? (No, no!)
君だけ見てるよ
I only have eyes for you!
偉いご褒美は？(チュウ)
Where's my praise and reward? (Chu!)
はーい！
Hoo!
ということで、ういはママ！
And with that, Uki Mama!
4周年おめでとう！
Happy anniversary!
ありがとうございます！いぇーい！
Thank you! Yay!
おめでとう！
Happy anniversary!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me!
えっ？
What?
ういはままと3Dできるの超嬉しい！
I'm so happy to be able to do 3D with Uki Mama!
ぽこぴーぶり？
It's been a while, hasn't it?
ぽこぴーぶり！
It really has!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
でもホロステージ初めて？
Is this your first time on Holo's stage?
初めてです！あっ、邪魔します！ あっ、邪魔します！
It is! Oh, sorry, sorry!
うちの上をよろしくお願いします！
We'll treat our upper stage nicely!
だまったって！
Quiet, quiet!
すごいステージだね、びっくりしたよ。
It's such an amazing stage, I was so surprised!
ねえ、見て見て、ここ！
And look, look over here!
ロゴがあるんだよ、ちょこ！
There's a logo, Choco-sensei!
あっ、しかもイラストもめっちゃ可愛い！
Oh, and the illustration is super cute too!
ねえ！ゆづりちゃんありがとう。
Right? Thanks for letting me join, Yuzuri-chan.
ありがとうございます！お疲れ様です！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いやー、一緒に歌って踊れる日が来るとは！
Man, the day I get to sing and dance with you like this...
そう、ちょこもさ…
Right? Choco-sensei too...
4周年呼んだら来てくれるかな、わくわくって思ってさ…
If I call you for your 4th anniversary, will you come? I was so excited thinking "Woohoo!"
そしたら、あっ行く行くつって、軽いのりで来ちゃったね。
And you were like, "Oh, I'll go!"—you accepted so quickly!
めっちゃね、即答でね、返事来たんよ。
I replied instantly, you know!
あたしもね、結構緊張してさ、思っとったんやけど。
I was so nervous beforehand, though!
こいつ…行く行くつって！
Look at this guy!
いや、そんな記念すべきね、ステージに呼んでいただけるなんてそれはもう頑張るしかないですよ。
Well, being invited to such a momentous stage is something we just have to give our all for!
きゅんきゅんだった！
It really was!
めっちゃ頑張って練習したかいがあったわ！
I practiced so hard, you know.
ねえ！ダンス頑張ってたもんね、ういはまー。
Right? You worked so hard on your dancing, Uki Mama!
もしかしてちょこ先生は余裕ですねぇ！
Choco-sensei made it look so easy, though!
さすが、これが4周年ってやつですか？
Well, this is what 4 years of experience looks like, you know!
いや、4年やってるんでね。
Yeah, I've been doing this for 4 years, so...
キャパシタが違うわ！
My capacity is different!
はい、ということで、せっかくだからちょこういはまなに、ういはまにお願いがあるんだぁ。
So, since Choco-sensei is here, I have a favor to ask!
で 私やる事終わったから帰ろうかな。
Well, I'm done with my part so I'm heading home!
あの あの あ、最後記念写真撮ってもらっていいですか？
Wait, wait, wait!
もう帰る気満々じゃんね！
You're going home already?!
もうやることないのかなって思って！
You're not doing it anymore?
あるよ！やだやだ、なんだよ、なんだよ！
Wait, wait! What is it? What is it?
撮り、撮りたい、おしゃ、おしゃし…
Take a photo with me!
赤ちゃん？ 赤ちゃん！
A cat ear pose? Red-chan!
なに、なにをしてほしいって？
What did you want me to do?
サメねのポーズ撮りた…
I want to take a shark pose photo.
えー？
Huh?
めっちゃ嬉しそうじゃんね！
You look so happy about it!
ねえ！
Hey!
はい。
Here.
なんか違うんだけど。
It feels a bit different, though.
なんか違う！
Something's off.
ういの方から来てくれるなんて！
For Uki to come all the way for me...
あーそんな慣れない慣れないなんて 4万年前の…
Oh, stop it with the "all the way"—it's like 4,000 years!
おい！おい、こら、うい、待って待って待って！
Hey! Come on, Uki, wait, wait, wait!
待て待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait!
こんなことしてていいの？
Is it okay to do stuff like this?
あ、ごめん。あの、一応ライブなんだよね。
Oh, sorry, this is a live stream after all!
そうだよ。
That's right.
まだまだあるんでしょ？
There's still more to come, right?
だから、頑張れるようにさ、うん。
So, to make sure I can give it my all,
みんなから可愛い応援が欲しいな…って！
I want everyone's cute cheers!
頑張れ！
You can do it!
頑張れ頑張れ頑張れ！
Do your best, do your best!
ってことで、いらっしゃれたのしぐれういでしたー！
And so, this has been Shigure Ui!
一緒に、いぇーい！
Together, yay!
ありがとー！ありがとー！
Thank you! Thank you!
頑張ってね。この後も頑張るちょこ！
Do your best. Good luck with the rest, Choco!
見てるよーん。
I'll be watching.
アノーののー アノーののー アノーののー さんさんウィーク！
Ano no no, ano no no, ano no no, sun sun week!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全力でレッツゴー！
With all our might, let's go!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全体進め！
Move forward, everyone!
一二三！
One, two, three!
気合い入れて (オスッ！)
Put your spirit into it (Osu!)
頑張って (ファイッ！)
Do your best (Fight!)
ハリキリ過ぎて空回り
Getting too excited and spinning our wheels
問題なし？ (うざい)
No problem? (Annoying)
ってこっそりと (ちょっとぉ！)
Whispering secretly (Hold on!)
フォローするとかずるい
Covering for each other is so unfair
なんたって毎日がそんな
After all, every single day is
目まぐるしくってもう
So dizzy and overwhelming,
目が回り回るようなハッピーデイズ
Like happy days where my head keeps spinning
不器用ななくらい直視できない
So clumsy I can't look straight ahead,
くすぐったいこの気持ちは何なんだろ
What is this ticklish feeling?
さんざんな今日だってきっと
Even on a rough day, I'm sure that
笑っちゃえばにっと ほら大丈夫だよ
If I just smile, look, it'll be alright!
まだまだこんなの想定内だよ
This is still all within expectations!
本音で語ったり
Talking honestly,
意外とほんのちょっと頼りて困ります
Surprisingly, it's a bit troubling when you rely on me
あー晴れた日だって 雨の日だって
Ah, whether it's a sunny day or a rainy day,
進んでいこう フレーフレーファイトだ
Let's keep moving forward, hip hip, fight!
レッツゴー社会人！
Let's go, working adults!
大吉ばかりならいいのにね
It'd be nice if it were all great blessings, but
今日は今日で今日も笑顔で頑張りましょう
Today is today, so let's keep smiling today too!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全力でレッツゴー！
With all our might, let's go!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全体進め！
Move forward, everyone!
一二三！
One, two, three!
嬉しくて (イェイ！)
Happy (Yay!)
ハイタッチ (ハイ！)
High-five (High!)
思わず微笑む昼下がり
Suddenly smiling in the afternoon
タイミング (ちょう！まじ！)
Timing (Super! Seriously!)
ばっちりで (まずまず)
Perfectly (First of all)
息止め当てはずいはずい
Holding my breath, missing the mark
あれもうこれもしや頭鳴ったりもしない
Wait, is this ringing in my head?
勘違いをおっしゃような大失敗 (はい！)
Mistakenly saying such a big blunder (Yes!)
時々しちゃうから
Sometimes I mess up like that,
良すぎたかな
Maybe it was too good?
そこで食い気味口を滑らせちゃうの
That's why I end up slipping my tongue
巡る巡るマイジーがいなって
Day after day goes by,
鳴いちゃうときっとお椀こと考えて
When I cry, I'm sure thinking about bowls of soup
笑っちゃえば何にもなっちゃうみたい
It seems like if I just laugh, it all disappears
口なんか聞いて
Listening to what people say,
くれてほんのちょっと勘違いしゃいまっす
I get a little ahead of myself and make a mistake
あー晴れた日だって
Ah, whether it's a sunny day
雨の日だって
Or a rainy day,
頑張ってここからだとしてもね
Let's do our best from here on
酸っぱいなんかわからないで
Don't be scared just because it's sour
今日は今日で
Today is today,
今日でも笑顔で頑張りましょう
So let's keep smiling today too!
悔しいことも嬉しいことも
Both frustrating things and happy things
ことも一緒に感じられる
We can feel them together
愛しい散々な日々が甘いお汁粉に溶けていく
Those lovely, rough days melt into sweet Oshiruko
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全力で進さんさんウィーク！
With all our might, sun sun week!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全力で進さんさんウィーク！
With all our might, sun sun week!
あすは好きでも本当に大好きですがもういい
Even if tomorrow is uncertain, I truly love it so much
行っちゃってきっと取っちゃえばにっと
If we just go and grab it with a smile,
ほら大丈夫だよまだまだこんなの想定内だよ
Look, it'll be alright! This is still all within expectations!
本音で語ったり意外とほんのちょっと頼りて困ります
Talking honestly, surprisingly it's a bit troubling when you rely on me
あー晴れた日だって 雨の日だって
Ah, whether it's a sunny day or a rainy day,
進んでいこう フレーフレーファイトだ
Let's keep moving forward, hip hip, fight!
敵地ばこでつまんない顔ね
Making a boring face in enemy territory
今日は今日で今日でも笑顔で頑張ろう
Today is today, so let's smile and do our best today too!
一緒に頑張ろう毎日楽しんじゃおう
Let's do our best together and enjoy every day!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全力で
With all our might!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sun sun week!
全体進め！
Move forward, everyone!
一二三！
One, two, three!
アノーののー アノーののー アノーののー さんさんウィーク！
Ano no no, ano no no, ano no no, sun sun week!
はーい、ということで
All right, so...
チョコ先生、4周年おめでとうございます！
Choco-sensei, congratulations on your 4th anniversary!
ありがとうございます！やったー！
Thank you so much! Yay!
いや、めちゃめちゃ久しぶりじゃない？お姉さん組が集まるの。
Man, it's been forever since the big sister group got together, hasn't it?
知らない人もいるかもしれない。
Some people might not even know us.
しらないわやめて。
Hey, don't say that!
我々ね、ASMRとかしてね、心を癒して下りますリスナーさんを。
We do ASMR and heal our listeners' hearts.
どうもお姉さん組、お姉さん組ですよ。
Hello, we're the big sister group.
これからうっとりしていくんで。
We're going to mesmerize you from here on.
いつかもっと出したいね。
We want to put out more someday.
出したい出したい。
We definitely want to!
はい、ということでね、ちょっとチョコ4周年なんで、
Yeah, so since it's Choco's 4th anniversary,
ちょっと二人にお願いしたいことがあって。
there's something I want to ask these two.
なになに？
What is it? What is it?
ちょっと二人にあまやかされたいの。
I want you two to spoil me a bit.
いやもっとあまやかしてよ！もっともっと頭なでなでしてよ！
No, spoil me more! Pat my head more and more!
二人のその…あー！
Those two being like... Ahh!
よしよし、頑張った！毎日頑張って偉いなー！可愛い、可愛い、好き好き、好き、いいこいいこ、よしよし
There, there, you worked hard! You did your best every day, so good! Cute, cute, I love you, good girl, there, there.
いや、でもね、本当ね、まだまたセクシーなんだよね、ちょっと作り方がちょっと誘ってるんだよね。
But you know, it's still kind of sexy. The way you make it is a bit seductive, you know.
でも、チョコ先生まだまだあるでしょ？戻ろうね。
But Choco-sensei, you still have more, right? Let's go back.
ここで崩れ落ちてたらね、だめだよ。
If you collapse here, that won't do.
まだまだね、がんばろう、もっともっとよ。
We've still got more to do, let's do our best, more and more.
じゃあ、最後にチョコにちょっと頑張れる…あどうし。
Well, finally, something to make Choco work hard... Ah, what should we do?
頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ！調子、調子！
Do your best, do your best, do your best...! Keep it up, keep it up!
チョコがんばるね！ありがと！
I'll do my best, Choco! Thank you!
よかった！だんだん恥ずかしくなってきてから帰ろう！帰ろう！帰ろう！がんばってね！ありがとう！
That's great! It's getting embarrassing, let's go home! Let's go! Do your best! Thank you!
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū-to!
髪型チェック！
Hair checked!
スカート穿いて
Wearing my skirt!
君に褒められる準備は万端
I'm all set to be praised by you!
袖をつかんだらキュンとする？
If I grab your sleeve, will it make your heart go doki?
つま先ふれたらドキッとするかしら
If our toes touch, will it make you flutter?
可愛いって言わせちゃうプランは完璧
My plan to make you call me cute is foolproof!
今日の私は無敵なの！
Today I'm invincible!
もはや天使？いや悪魔級にキュート！
Are you an angel? No, devilishly cute!
まいっちゃうでしょ！
It'll get to you!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
くらくらさせるわきみのこと
I'm gonna make your head spin,
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
めらめら燃えるこの心
This heart is burning bright!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
きみをふりむかせるためなら
If it's to make you look my way,
デビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
悪魔にだって魂売るわ！
I'd sell my soul to the devil!
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū-to!
なのにずるいわそんな笑顔で
Yet it's so unfair, with that smile of yours,
おはようなんて言われたら
when you tell me "Good morning,"
プランまっ白白旗だわ
my plan goes completely blank, it's a white flag.
まいっちゃうじゃない！
That's just cheating!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
くらくらさせるわきみのこと
I'm gonna make your head spin,
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
めらめら燃えるこの心
This heart is burning bright!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
きみをふりむかせるためなら
If it's to make you look my way,
デビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
悪魔にだって魂売るわ！
I'd sell my soul to the devil!
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū-to!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
フラフラしないでとなりにいて
Don't wander off, stay right by my side!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
キラキラしてるこの私
Look at me sparkling brightly!
デビデビデビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-debi-debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
きみを釘付けにできるなら
If I can keep you glued to me,
デビきゅー！デビcute！
Debi-kyū! Debi-cute!
悪魔にだって魂売るわ！
I'd sell my soul to the devil!
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū-to!
なのにずるいわそんな笑顔でおはようなんて言われたら
Yet it's so unfair, when you say "Good morning" with that smile,
プランまっ白白旗だわ
my plan goes completely blank, it's a white flag.
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū, Debikyū-to!
Debikyu, debikyu, debikyu, debikyuto!
よし！今日こそ 決めるわ！
Alright! Today's the day I'll win you over!
デビデビデビ級！ デビcute！ くらくらさせるわ きみのこと
Debi-debi-debi class! Debi-cute! You're making me dizzy!
デビデビデビ級！ デビcute！ めらめらもえる この心
Debi-debi-debi class! Debi-cute! My heart is burning up!
デビデビデビ級！ デビcute！ きみをふりむかす ためなら
Debi-debi-debi class! Debi-cute! If it means turning your head,
デビ級！ デビcute！ あくまにだって魂売るわ！
Debi class! Debi-cute! I'd sell my soul to a devil!
デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Debikyu, debikyu, debikyu, debikyuto!
はーい！ おめでとー！そこさん4周年おめでとー！ありがとー！
Yay! Congratulations! Happy 4th anniversary, Choco-san! Thank you!
おめでとー！ おめでとー！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
かっこいい！ お姉さま！ うらやましい！ うらやましい！
So cool! Big sis! So jealous! So jealous!
よかったねすー！ かっこよくてよかったね！
That's great! I'm so glad it was cool!
あれ？今日なんか清楚じゃない？とわ様。
Huh? Aren't you looking kind of pure today, Towa-sama?
えー！可愛いでしょ？ほら、珍しくかっこいいやつね、なんか。
Eh? Isn't it cute? See, it's unusually cool, you know.
とわ様がこういう曲歌うの。
Towa-sama singing a song like this.
え、あのさ、なんでこの曲選んだの？
Um, hey, why did you choose this song?
いや、これ悪魔組で、なんか歌いたいなって思って、最初かわいい曲かかっこいい曲かでめちゃめちゃ迷ったの、ちょこ。
Well, this is the devil group, and I wanted to sing something together, so I was super torn between a cute or cool song.
このメンバーだし、かっこいい曲も絶対合うけどでも絶対とわ様は歌わない可愛い曲を
With this lineup, a cool song would definitely fit, but a cute song that Towa-sama would never sing...
なんか、やっぱね自分じゃ歌いにくそうだからちょこがお誘いして一緒に歌いたいなって思って。
Well, since it's hard to sing on my own, I invited Choco so we could sing it together.
え、マジで？やだった？マジで？なになになに？
Eh, seriously? Did you hate it? Seriously? What, what, what?
え、これとわってちょこ先から誘われて、普通にいいよって言った？ラプラスは？
Eh, so Towa was invited by Choco-sen and just said "sure"? What about Laplace?
あ、もちろんもちろん！即答でいった！
Ah, of course, of course! Answered right away!
「いいですね！」って言って。「いいですね！」みたいな。
Saying "That sounds great!" Like "That sounds great!"
とわは一回渋ったよね？
Towa hesitated at first, right?
いや、ちょっと本当にこれ、この曲こなんで全部でいいの？みたいな。
No, I was like, wait, really, is this song... is this really okay for all of us?
いや、でもデビルだからぴったりですよ。
No, but since we're devils, it's a perfect fit.
そうそうそう。デビルで多分別人選んでくれてて一緒に歌ってくれてるの分かったから。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I knew you chose it because we're devils and wanted to sing together.
しかもちょこせいのね、記念だから歌うか！
And since it's Choco-sen's anniversary, I'll sing it!
やったー！なんかかっこよかったしかわいかったですね。
Yay! It was both cool and cute.
え？そうなの？そうなの？
Eh? Is that so? Is that so?
え、本当にね、ちょここれ欲望のままで選んだメンツだからね。
Eh, really, Choco chose this lineup purely based on her desires.
えー！初めて歌えてめちゃめちゃちょこにやにやしちゃった。
Eh! Singing it for the first time, Choco was grinning so much.
ちょこ先歌うの初めてだから！
Because it's Choco-sen's first time singing it!
え、てかもう3人目も初めてですよね？
Eh, wait, is it the first time for all three of us?
そうだよね！そうなのそうなの！
That's right! That's right, that's right!
だからここシナジーあるあるかもね、デビル。
So there might be some synergy here among us devils.
いや、デビル、デビル、デビル、デビル！
No, devil, devil, devil, devil!
デビルはあるけどね、でもこの中だったら我が一番角でかいんで、一番偉い。
Well, there are devils, but out of us, my horns are the biggest, so I'm the highest.
え？
Eh?
え、位で言うとどうなの？位で言うと。
Eh, in terms of rank, how is it? In terms of rank.
え、位で言うととわはちょこ先の下だよ。だって古悪魔だから。
Eh, in terms of rank, Towa is below Choco-sen. Because she's an ancient devil.
ちょこ先のほうがやっぱり大悪魔だから。
Choco-sen is a greater devil, after all.
いやでも、じゃあそんな悪魔の我が輩の方が角でかいし、我が輩がいちばん、すごいキリッとしてるしね、いちばん下だから。
No, but then, between those devils, my horns are bigger, and I'm the most sharp-looking since I'm at the bottom.
いちばんだからちいかわいちばーん！
Because I'm number one, Chii-kawa is number one!
なんで！
Why?!
はい、じゃあ最後に、ちょこから二人にお願いがあるの！
Alright, then lastly, Choco has a request for the two of you!
なんすか？何すか？
What is it? What is it?
なんかね、やっぱりみなさまを誘惑したいなって思って、三人で誘惑ポーズして終わりたいななんて思うんだよね。
Well, you see, I want to seduce everyone, and I thought we could end it by striking a seductive pose together.
誘惑ポーズね。ポーズだったらまあまあまあまあまあ…
A seductive pose, huh. If it's a pose, well, well, well...
え、本当ですか？誘惑ポーズはいいんですか？
Eh, really? Is a seductive pose okay?
いや、ちょっと我慢しやろっかなって思うんですけど。あ、せやせやせやせや！
No, I thought I'd hold back a bit. Ah, right, right, right!
足腰、足腰！ナイスすぎるな。
Legs and hips, legs and hips! That's too nice.
え、いいかな？いいかな？
Eh, is it okay? Is it okay?
まあ、まあじゃあ、はい。
Well, well then, okay.
誘惑ポーズですよね？
A seductive pose, right?
うん、誘惑ポーズ。いきますよ？カメラさん。
Yeah, a seductive pose. Here we go, camera-san.
できて？え？
Ready? Eh?
あ、そういう感じで、せーのでやります、せーので。
Ah, like that? We'll do it on three, on three.
なるほどね。
I see.
はい、渾身のやつ。渾身の一発！
Okay, our all-out pose. Our ultimate shot!
せーの！ぷ、ちょっと待ってちょっと待って！
Ready, set— wait, wait, wait!
え？終わり？
Eh? It's over?
欲望 喧騒 駆け引き 渦巻く アンダーシティ
Desire, commotion, bargaining, a swirling undercity
仕事 成功 夢 希望 求める 猛者達
Work, success, dreams, hope—sought by brave contenders
バーテン ディーラー ギャンブラー 集まる カジノで
Bartenders, dealers, gamblers gather in the casino
「貴女の大事なモノ、全部賭けましょう」
"Let's wager everything you hold dear."
今宵のgameは何だい?
What's tonight's game?
ほどよい刺激を頂戴
Give me just the right thrill.
ホイール廻して ボール落とす 簡単なゲーム
Spin the wheel, drop the ball—a simple game.
ダランベールなんて 退屈すぎるわ
D'Alembert is way too boring.
狙いは36倍
Aiming for 36x.
さあ、二人の舞台へ…いくよ?
Now, to our stage... ready?
目にも留まらぬ神業でshow time!!
Show time with god-like speed!
運命的なシチュエーションで 遊戯盤は廻り出す
The roulette wheel spins in a fateful situation.
完敗?失うのは「金」か「プライド」か?
Complete defeat? Will you lose "money" or "pride"?
瞳を閉じたその隙に 心ごと奪ってあげましょう
In the instant you close your eyes, I'll take your heart too.
羨望 幻想 溜息 渦巻く アンダーシティ
Envy, fantasy, sighs—a swirling undercity
裏切り 翻弄 自己破産 破れた猛者達
Betrayal, manipulation, bankruptcy—ruined brave contenders
成金 負犬 ペテン師 だらけのカジノで
In a casino full of upstarts, losers, and swindlers
「貴男の大事なモノ、全部賭けましょう」
"Let's wager everything you hold dear."
今宵のゲームは何だい?
What's tonight's game?
ほどよい刺激を頂戴
Give me just the right thrill.
トランプ5枚だけ揃える 簡単なゲーム
A simple game of collecting just 5 cards.
ブラフで攻めるなんて 退屈すぎるぜ?
Attacking with a bluff is way too boring, right?
狙いはdeal = jackpotのみ
Aiming solely for deal = jackpot.
さあ 二人の舞台へ…いくよ?
Now, to our stage... ready?
目にも留まらぬ神業でshow time!!
Show time with god-like speed!
運命的なシチュエーションで 遊戯盤は廻り出す
The roulette wheel spins in a fateful situation.
完敗?失うのは「夢」か「プライド」か?
Complete defeat? Will you lose "dreams" or "pride"?
瞳を閉じたその裏に 痛いほど刻んであげましょう
I'll carve it painfully deep behind your closed eyes.
最後のゲームは何だい?
What's the final game?
イカサマだらけの勝敗
Victory and defeat full of cheating.
サイコロ⇔ロールを繰り返す 簡単なゲーム
A simple game of repeating dice ⇔ rolls.
odds betで3倍 退屈すぎるわ
3x on odds bet is way too boring.
そろそろシロクロつけましょう
It's about time we settle this black and white.
二人の勝負へ…いくよ?
To our showdown... ready?
目にも留まらぬ神業でshow time!!
Show time with god-like speed!
絶対的なシチュエーションで 遊戯盤は廻り出す
The roulette wheel spins in an absolute situation.
完敗?失うのは「神」か「プライド」か?
Complete defeat? Will you lose "god" or "pride"?
瞳を閉じる暇もない? 心ごと壊してあげましょう
No time to close your eyes? I'll break your heart along with it.
目にも留まらぬ神業でshow time!!
Show time with god-like speed!
感動的なシチュエーションで 遊戯盤は廻り出す
The roulette wheel spins in a touching situation.
逆転?失ったのは「愛」か「プライド」か?
Reversal? Did you lose "love" or "pride"?
瞳を閉じたその隙に 心ごと奪ってあげましょう
In the instant you close your eyes, I'll take your heart too.
チョコ先輩 お疲れ様です！
Choco-senpai, great job!
いや、今日は お呼びいただきありがとうございます。そして、おめでとうございます！
Thank you so much for having me today. And congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いや、もうチョコ先輩の曲、かっこいい曲一緒に歌いたいと思って
I really wanted to sing a cool song together with Choco-senpai...
いや、めちゃくちゃ嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
そう、今回イカサマカジノのね、めちゃくちゃかっこいいからね、めちゃくちゃチョコ好きな曲だからね、一緒に歌えてめちゃくちゃ嬉しい！
Yes, "Ikasama Casino" is super cool, and since it's a song Choco loves so much, I'm so happy we could sing it together!
やったーー！ いつも可愛いな、もうチョコ先輩は。
Yay! Choco-senpai is always so cute.
いや、もうそんな、ちゃ、今日のこの可愛くてかっこいい姿を一緒に、パシャリしてくれる？
Oh come on... would you take a snapshot together of today's cute and cool look?
もちろん！
Of course!
え、じゃあちょっとレイ様のバイショット教えてもらっていいですか？
Um, could you tell me Ray-sama's bye spot?
オッケーです。
Okay.
じゃあ、行きましょうか。
Then, shall we go?
ジャンプしていきますよ！せーのっ！
We'll jump! Ready, set!
はいっ！
Yes!
はい、こちらがバイスポットです。どうどう？
Here is the bye spot. How is it?
え、めちゃくちゃかっこいい！ そう、私のねステージを選んでくれたので、ご紹介させていただきましたが。
Wow, super cool! Since you chose my stage, I introduced it.
じゃあ、ここで やりますか？
Shall we do it here?
え、じゃあピースでいく？
Um, shall we go with peace signs?
背中合わせでじゃあ... 背中合わせでじゃあ
Back-to-back then... back-to-back then
イエーイ！
Yay!
写真撮ってるかな？みんな。
I wonder if everyone's taking pictures?
うん
Mm.
うん、いいですね。
Mm, sounds good.
くねくねくねくね
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
いや、かわいい！
So cute!
いや、いつも料理ばっか、ね、一緒にしてるから、歌うってめちゃくちゃ新鮮ですね。
Since we're always just cooking together, singing feels so super fresh.
確かに。
That's true.
え、みんなどうだった？どうだった？
So, everyone, how was it? How was it?
リッチショコラの歌、最高だったでしょ？
Rich Choco's song was amazing, right?
歌も美味しかった？
Was the song delicious too?
うんうん。
Yeah, yeah.
で、何かチョコ宣伝あるんですか？この後？
And is there any Choco announcement after this?
あ、そう！せっかくだから、ルイさまにサプライズ用意したの、チョコ。
Ah, that's right! Since we have the chance, Choco prepared a surprise for Lui-sama.
おお、なんだろう？
Oh, what is it?
じゃ、ルイさん行きますよ。
Well then, Lui-san, let's go.
はい。
Okay.
じゃ、一緒にせーの、で！
Then, together, on 3, ready, go!
おお！やった！
Oh! Yay!
え、ダーツだ！
Eh, darts!
なんですか？ダーツゲームするの今から？
What's this? Are we playing a darts game now?
そうそうそうそう、ルイさまにこれからダーツゲームしてもらおうかなって思って。
Yes, yes, yes, I thought I'd have Lui-sama play a darts game.
おお、やりましょ、やりましょ！
Oh, let's do it, let's do it!
ぜひぜひ！
Definitely!
じゃ、じゃ、じゃ、お願いしまーす。
Well then, please.
なんですか？
What is it?
ブルはチョコ。
Bullseye is Choco.
え、チョコのブルは、じゃあどこかな？ここかな？
Eh, where is Choco's bullseye? Here?
ただいま映像が乱れております。しばらくお待ち下さい。
The video feed is currently disrupted. Please wait a moment.
雨上上がりの虹も 凛と咲いた花も 色づき溢れ出す
The rainbow after the rain, the flowers blooming proudly, overflowing with color,
茜色の空仰ぐ君に あの日恋に落ちた
I looked up at the crimson sky and fell in love with you that day.
瞬間のドラマチック フィルムの中の1コマも 消えないよ 心に刻むから
Not a single frame of that dramatic moment will fade; I'll engrave it in my heart.
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
It's you, it's you who taught me that if darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に もう隠さないで 煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Turn your sadness into a smile, don't hide it; every sparkling star will shine upon you.
眠りも忘れて迎えた朝日は やたらと突き刺す
The morning sun greeting us without sleep pierces right through us,
低気圧運ぶ 頭痛だって 忘れる 君に会えば
I even forget the headache brought by low pressure when I see you.
静寂は浪漫チック 紅茶に溶けた砂糖のように 全身に巡るよ 君の声
Silence is romantic; your voice flows through my body like sugar melting in tea.
君だよ 君なんだよ 笑顔をくれた 涙も光るなら 流星になる
It's you, it's you who gave me a smile; if my tears shine, they become shooting stars.
傷付いたその手を もう離さないで 願いを込めた空に 明日が来るから
Don't let go of my wounded hand anymore; tomorrow will come to the sky filled with wishes.
導いてくれた 光は君だよ つられて僕も走り出した
The light that guided me was you; I was drawn in and started running too.
知らぬ間に クロスし始めた ほら 今だ ここで 光るなら
Before I knew it, our paths began to cross. Look, now, if it shines here!
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇は終わるから
It's you, it's you who taught me that the darkness will end!
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
It's you, it's you who taught me that if darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に もう隠さないで 煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Turn your sadness into a smile, don't hide it anymore; every sparkling star will shine upon you.
答えはいつでも 偶然?必然? いつか選んだ道こそ 運命になる
Are answers always coincidence or fate? Someday the path we choose will become our destiny.
握りしめたその希望も不安も きっと二人を動かす 光になるから
The hopes and anxieties we hold tightly will surely become the light that moves us both.
雨上がりの虹も 凛と咲いた花も 色づき溢れ出す
The rainbow after the rain, the flowers blooming proudly, overflowing with color,
茜色の空仰ぐ君に あの日恋に落ちた
I looked up at the crimson sky and fell in love with you that day.
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
It's you, it's you who taught me that if darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に もう隠さないで 煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Turn your sadness into a smile, don't hide it anymore; every sparkling star will shine upon you.
導いてくれた 光は君だよ つられて僕も走り出した
The light that guided me was you; I was drawn in and started running too.
知らぬ間に クロスし始めた ほら 今だ ここで 光るなら
Before I knew it, our paths began to cross. Look, now, if it shines here!
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇は終わるから
It's you, it's you who taught me that the darkness will end!
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
It's you, it's you who taught me that if darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に もう隠さないで 煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Turn your sadness into a smile, don't hide it anymore; every sparkling star will shine upon you.
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた 暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
It's you, it's you who taught me that if darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に もう隠さないで 煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Turn your sadness into a smile, don't hide it anymore; every sparkling star will shine upon you.
煌めくどんな星も 君を照らすから
Every sparkling star will shine upon you.
答えはいつでも 偶然?必然?
Are answers always coincidence or fate?
雨上りの虹も
The rainbow after the rain,
凛と咲いた花も
the flowers blooming with dignity,
色づき溢れ出す
overflowing with color,
茜色の空仰ぐ君に あの日恋に落ちた
I looked up at you in the crimson sky, falling in love that day.
瞬間のドラマティック
The dramatic moment,
フィルムの中の1コマも
not even a single frame of the film
消えないよ 心に刻むから
will fade, as I'll engrave it in my heart.
君だよ 君なんだよ 教えてくれた
It's you, it's you who taught me
暗闇も光るなら 星空になる
that if the darkness shines, it becomes a starry sky.
君に出逢えた喜びと
Taking the joy of meeting you
君に会えない淋しさの
and the loneliness of not seeing you,
両方を手に入れて恋は走り出す
love takes hold of both and starts to run.
空も飛べない僕だけど
Though I cannot fly through the sky,
孤独を歌う夜だけど
though it's a night of singing solitude,
その頬に微笑みを与えられたなら
if I can bring a smile to those cheeks,
初めて君を抱きしめた瞬間に 神様に下した使命は君だけのヒーロー
the moment I first held you close, the mission God gave me was to be your sole hero.
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと夢中にさせてあげるからね
I'll make you even more captivated, you know?
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be your pop star
君をぎゅっと抱きしめてあげるからおいで
come here so I can hold you tight in my arms,
キラキラの pop star
a sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you,
君だけに
just for you.
隠していた闇も
Even the darkness I tried to hide,
君はそっと拾い上げて
you gently picked it up
大切な僕なんだと抱きしめてくれた
and held me tight, saying I am precious to you.
光へと続く道を歩いて行こう
Let's walk down the path leading to the light.
傷かばおうこの右手は 君と手をつなぐために
This right hand that shields my wounds is to hold hands with you.
You're gonna be my pop star
僕をもっと夢中にさせてよ 微笑んで
make me even more captivated, smile!
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて
cast your magic on me with those eyes.
You're my only pop star
僕をぎゅっと抱きしめたらもう離さない
if you hold me tight, I'll never let you go.
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて 今すぐに
cast your magic on me with those eyes right now.
恋に落ちたら誰もが誰かの pop star
When you fall in love, anyone becomes someone's pop star.
神様に下した使命は君だけのヒーロー
The mission God gave me was to be your sole hero.
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと夢中にさせてあげるからね
I'll make you even more captivated, you know?
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be your pop star
君をぎゅっと抱きしめてあげるからおいで
come here so I can hold you tight in my arms,
キラキラの pop star
a sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
隠していた暗闇も
Even the darkness I tried to hide,
君はそっと拾い上げて
you gently picked it up
大切な僕なんだと抱きしめてくれた
and held me tight, saying I am precious to you.
光へと続く道を歩いて行こう
Let's walk down the path leading to the light.
傷かばおうこの右手は 君と手をつなぐために
This right hand that shields my wounds is to hold hands with you.
You're gonna be my pop star
僕をもっと夢中にさせてよ 微笑んで
make me even more captivated, smile!
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて
cast your magic on me with those eyes.
You're my only pop star
僕をぎゅっと抱きしめたらもう離さない
if you hold me tight, I'll never let you go.
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて 今すぐに
cast your magic on me with those eyes right now.
You're gonna be my pop star
僕をもっと夢中にさせてよ 微笑んで
make me even more captivated, smile!
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて
cast your magic on me with those eyes.
You're my only pop star
僕をぎゅっと抱きしめたらもう離さない
if you hold me tight, I'll never let you go.
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
その瞳で僕に魔法をかけて 今すぐに
cast your magic on me with those eyes right now.
恋に落ちたら誰もが誰かの pop star
When you fall in love, anyone becomes someone's pop star.
神様に下した使命は君だけのヒーロー
The mission God gave me was to be your sole hero.
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと夢中にさせてあげるからね
I'll make you even more captivated, you know?
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be your pop star
君をぎゅっと抱きしめてあげるからおいで
come here so I can hold you tight in my arms,
キラキラの pop star
a sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと夢中にさせてあげるからね
I'll make you even more captivated, you know?
キラキラの pop star
A sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be your pop star
君をぎゅっと抱きしめてあげるからおいで
come here so I can hold you tight in my arms,
キラキラの pop star
a sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
I wanna be your pop star
君をぎゅっと抱きしめてあげるからおいで
come here so I can hold you tight in my arms,
キラキラの pop star
a sparkling pop star,
羽根を広げ魔法をかけてあげるよ
I'll spread my wings and cast magic for you.
君だけに
Just for you.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
おめでとうございます！
Happy anniversary!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
まさか放送中にポップスターになってしまうとは！
Who would've thought we'd become pop stars during the stream?!
え、なんでポップスターになってるんだっけ？
Wait, why did we become pop stars again?
カッキーのせいでしょ、ほら、忘れるな忘れるな！
Because of Kakki! Hey, don't forget!
なんだなんだ、何？
What, what? What is it?
いや、こいつが日向バーチャーンとか言い出したんだよ。
Well, this one started calling herself Hinata Virtual and stuff!
あ、そっからか！ 伏線回収がなかなかできなくてさ。
Ah, from there! We couldn't resolve the foreshadowing...
なんかちょっと全部思い出しくない思い出かもしれない。 まぶしっかくよ。
It might be memories we don't want to recall. So dazzling!
あれか！
Is that it?
いやでもね、本当ね、4周年おめでとうだね、チョコ先生。
Well, truly, congratulations on your 4th anniversary, Choco-sensei!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
一周年にして！ ありがとう、ありがとう！
On our 1st anniversary— Thank you, thank you!
なんかちょっとあれだね、セレブリティな香りがするんだよね。
It has a sort of celebrity scent to it, doesn't it?
え、ほんと？ セレブリティっぽい？
Really? Does it feel like a celebrity?
ここの二人めちゃめちゃセレブリティの香りするよ。
These two right here have a huge celebrity vibe.
あ、ほんとだ。
Oh, true!
なんか某姉妹みたい。
Sort of like certain sisters.
ねえ、なんかちょっと地味なんだ けど、気のせいかもしれない。
Hey, it's a bit subdued, maybe it's just my imagination.
うんうん。
Yeah, yeah.
なんだよ、この最後をつけたって。
What's with adding "in the end" like that?
いやいやいや、うちらと言ったらさ、
No, no, when you say us,
スワチョコルーナといったら、なんかこれがある。ないよ！
For SuwaChocoLuna, there's this— No way!
変なイメージをつけるなよ。まさかこんなの。
Don't give us weird images! No way something like this.
ノイコな、おかしな、その顔をやめてくれよ！
Noiko, strange, stop making that face!
ちょっと、ルーナたが一番面白いんだよな。 確かに。
Luna is the funniest one of all. True!
ででで、ここに座って！ ここに座って！ ありがとうございます！ 変身しちゃうんだって、こいつ！
Sit here! Sit here! Thank you! She's gonna transform!
夜見たらちょっとびっくりするタイプ。
The type that startles you if you see it at night.
しかも終わったし。確かにな。
Plus it's already over. True that.
あい、ちょっと塩風ポーズとかできんじゃない。
Can we do a salty breeze pose or something?
塩風？ いや、塩風じゃなくて、塩分なんかなんか違うって。
Salty breeze? No, not salty breeze, saltiness... that's different.
なんか近くね？ なんか遠いみたい。 なんか近くね？
Isn't it close? Seems kinda far. Isn't it close?
あ、でもなんかね、塩は振ってそうな感じする。振ってそうな感じしてるでしょ。
Ah, but you know, it feels like salt is being sprinkled.
塩。
Salt.
どう？ こう？
How? Like this?
いや、何のポーズやねんこれ。塩風。
What kind of pose is that?! Salt breeze!
はい、じゃあ皆さんそろそろね帰る時間だね。 4周年おめでとうございます！ おめでとう、チョコ先生、おめでとう！
Alright, time to go home. Congratulations, Choco-sensei!
お待たせー！ ということで、ここで皆様に2つ告知があります。
Sorry to keep you waiting! We have two announcements for you all.
まず1つ目が、
First of all, the first one is...
タダドー！ なんとなんと！ 柚子チョコ活動4周年記念グッズが発売開始されます！
Tadaa! Yuzuki Choco's 4th Anniversary Goods go on sale!
21時からね。
Starting at 9 PM.
こちら内容の方がタダドー！
And the contents are... Tadaa!
市川春先生描き下ろしの、アクリルスマホスタンド！
Acrylic smartphone stand, illustrated specially by Haru Ichikawa!
そして、2つ目！ なんと皆様、お待たせいたしました！ チョコラのぬいぐるみ！ かわいい！
And second! Sorry to keep you waiting! Chocola plushie! Cute!
そして、3つ目は、 いやこれ待ってた人いるんじゃないかな。
And third, I bet there are people waiting for this.
こちら、チョコ先生のエプロン！ 山ケコとクッキングとかね、リッチチョコとかで、チョコがいつも持ってるエプロンです！
Choco-sensei's apron, worn in Yamakeko Cooking and Rich Choco!
そして4つ目は、 まあね、作った料理を盛っているのはもちろんこのミニプレート！ いやめちゃめちゃ可愛くないですか？
And fourth, this mini-plate for serving dishes! Isn't it super cute?
そして、チョコの耳舐めASMRボイス！
And, Choco's ear-licking ASMR voice!
ちゃんとね、チョコ描き下ろし台本でなってるので、ぜひぜひ皆様、はすはすしながら聞いてください！
It's from an original script, so please listen while panting!
まあね、今回ももちろん特典ございます！
And of course, there are special bonuses!
柚子チョコ直筆サイン入りポストカードです！ こちら直筆メッセージもちゃんと付いてきます！
Autographed postcard with a handwritten message!
今回はね、1枚1枚ちゃんとチョコ手書きでメッセージ入れるんで、メッセージじゃないや、サイン入れるので、チョコの直筆サインペロペロしちゃってください！
Please lick Choco's handwritten autograph!
そして、告知その2は、 このあとすぐなので、みんなお楽しみにな！
And announcement #2 is right after this, look forward to it!
ゴシップを並べては見栄張らないで
Lining up gossip, don't put on airs.
いくつだなんてゴミ箱へ
"How old are you?" throw that in the trash.
身に覚えあるんでしょさあ
You remember it, right? Come on.
チクチク痛いのね
It pricks and hurts, doesn't it?
エゴイズムに踊らされて
Dancing to egoism,
傷だらけで歩いてく　あーね　あーね
walking around covered in wounds—ah, right, ah, right.
シニア気取ってあくまでも
Acting like seniors, no matter what,
癒やしてあげるからさあお目覚めですか？
I'll heal you, so are you finally awake?
Dindong Dindong 踏み鳴らし Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, stomp away, Dindong,
笑い合って　ハッハッと叫べ
laughing together, shouting "ha-ha!"
Dindong Dindong 鳴らせよ Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, ring it out, Dindong,
病む顔がお好きか
do you like suffering faces?
Do you like suffering faces?
噛み付き合いの日々は　慰めもないわ
Days of biting each other offer no comfort.
私のものね　明日のNoDistance
You're mine, tomorrow's NoDistance.
サビにまみれ毎日こりごり懲りてく
Covered in rust, getting tired of it every day,
錆びた鎖繋いでテワクドイテく　冴えない姿だけで瞳を隠してく
Connecting rusty chains, hiding your dull appearance.
金槌か痛めのね
It hurts like a hammer, doesn't it?
エゴイズムに踊らされて
Dancing to egoism,
くず折れてく　あーね　あーね
collapsing—ah, right, ah, right.
シニア気取ってあくまでも
Acting like seniors, no matter what,
癒やしてあげるからさあ　求めてますか？
I'll heal you, so are you asking for it?
Dindong Dindong 狂わせ Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, drive them crazy, Dindong,
最後にハッハッと叫べ
finally shouting "ha-ha!"
Dindong Dindong 迷わぬ Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, unwavering, Dindong,
覚めぬうちに 口付けを
before waking up, give a kiss.
Dindong Dindong 踏み鳴らし Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, stomp away, Dindong,
笑い合って　ハッハッと叫べ
laughing together, shouting "ha-ha!"
Dindong Dindong 鳴らせよ Dindong
Dindong, Dindong, ring it out, Dindong,
病む顔がお好きか　病む顔がお好きか
do you like suffering faces? Suffering faces?
噛み付き合いの日々は　慰めもないわ
Days of biting each other offer no comfort.
私のものね　明日のNoDistance
You're mine, tomorrow's NoDistance.
明日のNoDistance
Tomorrow's NoDistance.
はーい　どうもねみんな
Hi there, everyone!
今回のこのオリジナル曲めちゃめちゃカッコよくないですかー？
Isn't this original song super, super cool?
と言うことで今回のこのオリジナル曲なんと
That's why, this original song...
本日24時配信開始プラス！
releases today at midnight, plus!
24時にこのオリジナル曲のMVが公開されるので大事に見ようね？
The MV for this original song will be premiered at midnight, so make sure to watch it!
24時待ってるね。
I'll be waiting at midnight.
それではオリジナル曲とかグッズとかのURLも概要欄チェックしてください！
So please check the description for URLs to the song and merch!
そして本日の最後まで見ていただいてご視聴いただきありがとうございました！
And thank you so much for watching all the way to the end today!
Thank you for watching my cute students!